## Tomas Alejandro V. Falgui III

tomyfalguiiii@yahoo.com — http://tomyfalgui.com

#### contact details

Tomas Alejandro V. Falgui III 09171139313 tomyfalguiii@yahoo.com

#### technical skills

Well versed in web development technologies such as HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. Advanced in ReactJS and familiar with VueJS. Experienced also in building server-side technologies with NodeJS, Python(Django), and Elixir(Phoenix). Skilled at reading and writing code after accurate assessment of coding requirements. Knowledgeable on UI design and is able to implement responsive web designs.

#### •Languages

Programming— Python, Elixir, Lisp, JavaScript, JavaMarkup— LATEX, HTML, CSS

### education

Dole Philippines School (2006 - 2018)

Ateneo de Manila University Batch2022/2023 - Computer Science and Digital Game Design and Development

# job experience

Freelance Web Developer (2019 - present)

User Experience Society Front End Engineer Officer (2018-2019)

User Experience Society Vice President for Backend Engineering (2019-2020)

### events participated

Facebook Workplace Hackathon Participant held on November 9-10 2018 at Facebook Manila CompSat Blue Hacks Participant held on February 23-24 2019 at Ateneo de Manila University DISCS Programming Open (Collegiate Level) Champion held on March 2, 2019 at Ateneo de Manila University